let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Lateral epicondylitis is also known as",
    answer: "tennis elbow",
    options: [
      "hockey elbow",
      "tennis elbow",
      "swimmers elbow",
      "golfers elbow",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: ".Which is NOT a common cause of injury for an elbow sprain",
    answer: "forced hyperflexion",
    options: [
      "valgus force",
      "varus force",
      "forced hyperextension",
      "forced hyperflexion"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is a bursa",
    answer: "fluid filled sac that protects the joint",
    options: [
      "tendon that connects to the olecranon",
      "joint capsule around the elbow joint",
      "fluid filled sac that protects the joint",
      "ligament that surrounds the olecranon"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which force comes from the medial side and puts stress on the lateral side of the joint? (At the elbow it would put stress on the RCL)",
    answer: "valgus",
    options: [
      "rotation",
      "valgus",
      "varus",
      "shear"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which ligament is on the medial side of the elbow?",
    answer: "UCL",
    options: [
      "Annular Ligament",
      "RCL",
      "UCL",
      "valgus",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The questions in this segment consist of two statements, one labeled asassertionand the other labeled as the reason. You are to examine these two statements carefully and decide ifassertion A and reason R are individually true and if so, whether the reason is a correct explanation of the assertion. Select your answers to these items using the codes given below. Assertion (A): The elbow joint is a hinge joint. ",
    answer: "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A.",
    options: [
      "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation of A.",
      "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A.",
      "is true but R is false.",
      "A is false but R is true"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which type of movement would have been possible ifour elbow had a fixed joint?",
    answer: "A fixed joint does not allow any movement. Thus, if our elbow had a fixed joint, we would not be able to bend/fold our arms",
    options: [
      "A fixed joint does not allow any movement. Thus, if our elbow had a fixed joint, we would not be able to bend/fold our arms",
      "A ball and socket joint allows movement in all directions. Thus, if we were to have a ball and socket joint between our neck and head, we would be able to rotate our head 360∘.",
      "None of the above",
      "Both of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which type of movement would have been possible if we were to have a ball and socket joint between our neck and head",
    answer: "A ball and socket joint allows movement in all directions. Thus, if we were to have a ball and socket joint between our neck and head, we would be able to rotate our head 360∘.",
    options: [
      "A fixed joint does not allow any movement. Thus, if our elbow had a fixed joint, we would not be able to bend/fold our arms",
      "A ball and socket joint allows movement in all directions. Thus, if we were to have a ball and socket joint between our neck and head, we would be able to rotate our head 360∘.",
      "none of the above",
      "Both of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The joint in our elbow is an example of",
    answer: "hinge joint",
    options: [
      "hinge joint",
      "ball and socket joint",
      "pivot joint",
      "gliding joint"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following joints does not allow any movement?",
    answer: "Fibrous joint",
    options: [
      "Synovial joint",
      "Fibrous joint",
      "Ball and Socket joint",
      "Cartilaginous joint"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Give the function of the Neurovasculature",
    answer: "Both a and b",
    options: [
      "The arterial supply to the cubital joint is from the cubital anastomosis, which incorporates recurrent and collateral branches from the brachial and deep brachial arteries.",
      "Its nerve supply is provided by the median, musculocutaneous and radial nerves anteriorly, and also the nervus ulnaris posteriorly.",
      "Both a and b",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The function of the Flexion is",
    answer: "all of the above",
    options: [
      "Being a hinge joint, the sole movements allowed by the elbow are flexion and extension of the joint and rotation of the radius",
      "The range of motion of the elbow is prescribed by the olecranon of the ulna, so the elbow can only touch around 180 degrees.",
      "Flexion of the elbow is prescribed only by the compression of soft tissues surrounding the joint.",
      "all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "which is true about the elbow?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "elbow is the joint connecting the upper arm to the forearm. ",
      "It’s classed as a hinge-type diarthrosis. ",
      "The rounded distal end of the humerus is split into two joint processes — the trochlea on the medial side and also the capitulum on the lateral side. ",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The elbow is a complex joint which is also known as a synovial joint, it is formed by the articulation of the three bones such as?",
    answer: "all of the above",
    options: [
      "Humerus",
      "Radius",
      "Ulna",
      "all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is false?",
    answer: "One of the muscles that comprise the forearm's interior compartment is the brachioradialis.",
    options: [
      "One of the muscles that comprise the forearm's interior compartment is the brachioradialis.",
      "It forms the lateral wall of the cubital fossa and is the most superficial muscle on the radial side of the forearm. ",
      "While the brachioradialis connects the upper arm to the forearm, the brachialis is the muscle that sits between the bicep and triceps. ",
      "The climber can clasp harder and pull through to the next hold more effortlessly if these two muscle groups are interconnected tightly."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "which of the following is false?",
    answer: "The climber cannot clasp harder and pull through to the next hold more effortlessly if these two muscle groups are interconnected tightly.",
    options: [
      "One of the muscles that comprise the forearm's posterior compartment is the brachioradialis.",
      "It forms the lateral wall of the cubital fossa and is the most superficial muscle on the radial side of the forearm",
      "While the brachioradialis connects the upper arm to the forearm, the brachialis is the muscle that sits between the bicep and triceps. ",
      "The climber cannot clasp harder and pull through to the next hold more effortlessly if these two muscle groups are interconnected tightly."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which of the following is not a movement of the elbow",
    answer: "Superposition",
    options: [
      "flexion",
      "extensiont",
      "supination",
      "Superposition"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which one of the following is false?",
    answer: "The joint that joins the lower arm to the forearm is known as the elbow",
    options: [
      "The joint that joins the lower arm to the forearm is known as the elbow",
      "It is categorized as a synovial joint of the hinge type. ",
      "The portion that surrounds the elbow joint, located between the arm and the forearm, is known as the elbow. ",
      "The cubital fossa, also described as the chelidon or the elbow pit, the lateral and medial epicondyles of the humerus, and the olecranon are keyways located in the elbow."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Which one of the following is false?",
    answer: "The portion that surrounds the elbow joint, located between the arm and the forearm, is known as the knee. ",
    options: [
      "The joint that joins the upper arm to the forearm is known as the elbow.",
      "It is categorized as a synovial joint of the hinge type. ",
      "The portion that surrounds the elbow joint, located between the arm and the forearm, is known as the knee. ",
      "The cubital fossa, also described as the chelidon or the elbow pit, the lateral and medial epicondyles of the humerus, and the olecranon are keyways located in the elbow."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which of the following is false?",
    answer: "The capsule is wide and mostly made up of transverse fibres on the posterior side.",
    options: [
      "The elbow joint contains a capsule encasing it, much like other synovial joints do. ",
      "This supports the joint since it is robust and fibrous on its own. ",
      "Collateral ligaments are created by medial and lateral thickening of the joint capsule, which stabilizes the arm's flexing and extending action. ",
      "The capsule is wide and mostly made up of transverse fibres on the posterior side."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Which of the following is false?",
    answer: "This supports the joint since it is robust and non-fibrous on its own. ",
    options: [
      "The elbow joint contains a capsule encasing it, much like other synovial joints do. ",
      "This supports the joint since it is robust and non-fibrous on its own. ",
      "Collateral ligaments are created by medial and lateral thickening of the joint capsule, which stabilizes the arm's flexing and extending action. ",
      "The capsule is narrow and mostly made up of transverse fibres on the posterior side."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Which of the following is false?",
    answer: "It increases friction between a joint's moving components as a cushion, preventing degenerative damage.",
    options: [
      "The capsule penetrates the annular ligament's posterior portion on the ulnar side. ",
      "Because of its link to the triceps tendon, the posterior capsule is shielded from compression during extension. ",
      "A bursa is a synovial fluid-filled membranous pouch. ",
      "It increases friction between a joint's moving components as a cushion, preventing degenerative damage."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Which of the following is false?",
    answer: "The capsule penetrates the annular ligament's interiorportion on the ulnar side.",
    options: [
      "The capsule penetrates the annular ligament's interiorportion on the ulnar side. ",
      "Because of its link to the triceps tendon, the posterior capsule is shielded from compression during extension. ",
      "A bursa is a synovial fluid-filled membranous pouch. ",
      "It decreases friction between a joint's moving components as a cushion, preventing degenerative damage."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "Joints are the",
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
    options: [
      "places where two parts of our body seem to be joined",
      "the points of contact between two(or more) bones together with tissues that surround it",
      "the points of contact between two(or more) bones",
      "Both (a) and (b)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Which one of the following has a different type of joint than the others?",
    answer: "Shoulder",
    options: [
      "Finger",
      "Elbow",
      "Knee",
      "Shoulder"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "The elbow joint",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "is a hinge joint",
      "allows only a back-and-forth movement",
      "allows movement in one direction only",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Read the passage (s) given below and answer the questions that follow Passage - 1 The places in our body where two parts of our body seem to be joined are called a joint, e.g. in the elbow different bones are joined together. We can bend or move our bodies only at those points where bones meet. There are many different types of joints in our body to help in carrying out different movements and activities. The joint where our head joins the neck is a",
    answer: " pivotal joint",
    options: [
      "hinge joint",
      " pivotal joint",
      "joint that allows movement in all directions",
      "ball and socket joint"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "The questions in this segment consist of two statements, one labeled as assertionand the other labeled as reason R. You are to examine these two statements carefully and decide if assertion A and reason R are individually true and if so, whether the reason is a correct explanation of the assertion. Select your answers to these items using the codes given below. Assertion (A): The elbow joint is a hinge joint.",
    answer: "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A.",
    options: [
      "Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation of A.",
      "Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of A.",
      "A is true but R is false.",
      "A is false but R is true."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Which of the following is not a movement of the elbow",
    answer: "vibration",
    options: [
      "vibration",
      "extension",
      "supination",
      "pronation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "which of the following is false?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Below the common extensor tendon, the radial collateral ligament is related to the lateral epicondyle. ",
      "This ligament mixes into the circumferential ligament of the radius and is less defined than the ulnar collateral ligament. ",
      "Its edges are anchored close to the radial notch of the ulna.",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
];